<resources>
    <string name="app_name">spaceUs</string>

    <string name="places">Study Places</string>
    <string name="err_msg_enter_username">Please enter username.</string>
    <string name="err_msg_enter_email">Please enter email.</string>
    <string name="err_msg_enter_phoneNum">Please enter contact number.</string>
    <string name="err_msg_enter_password">Please enter password.</string>
    <string name="err_msg_enter_confirmPassword">Please enter confirm password.</string>
    <string name="err_msg_enter_password_and_confirm_password_mismatch">Password and confirm password does not match.</string>
    <string name="err_msg_enter_agree_terms_and_condition">Please agree terms and condition.</string>
    <string name="register_Successful">Thanks for registering!</string>
    <string name="email_sent_success">\"Email sent successfully to reset your password! \"</string>
    <string name="register_success">You are registered successfully.</string>
    <string name="read_storage_permission_denied">Oops, you just denied the permission for storage. You can also allow it from settings.</string>
    <string name="image_selection_failed">Image selection Failed!</string>
    <string name="msg_profile_update_success">Your profile is updated successfully.</string>
    <string name="clear_all">CLEAR ALL</string>
    <string name="apply">APPLY</string>
    <string name="bus_from_mrt">Bus from MRT</string>
    <string name="walk_from_mrt">Walk from MRT</string>
    <string name="transport">TRANSPORT</string>
    <string name="plug_points">Plug Points</string>
    <string name="restrooms">Restrooms</string>
    <string name="wifi">WiFi</string>
    <string name="filter_places_by">FILTER PLACES BY</string>
    <string name="todo">TODO</string>


    <!--<string name="title_activity_dashboard">DashboardActivity</string> -->
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_search">Search</string>
    <string name="title_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="please_click_back_again_to_exit">Please click back again to exit</string>


    <!--TERMS & CONDITIONS section-->
    <string name="termsCond1">By downloading or using the app, these terms will automatically
        apply to you – you should make sure therefore that you read them carefully before using the
        app. </string>
    <string name="termsCond2">
        You’re not allowed to copy, or modify the app, any part of the app, or our trademarks
        in any way. You’re not allowed to attempt to extract the source code of the app, and you
        also should not try to translate the app into other languages, or make derivative versions.
        The app itself, and all the trade marks, copyright, database rights and other intellectual
    property rights related to it, still belong to Spaceus. </string>
    <string name="termsCond3">
        Spaceus is committed to ensuring that the app is as useful and efficient as possible.
        For that reason, we reserve the right to make changes to the app or to charge for its
        services, at any time and for any reason. We will never charge you for the app or its
        services without making it very clear to you exactly what you’re paying for. </string>
    <string name="termsCond4">
        The Spaceus app stores and processes personal data that you have provided to us, in order to
        provide our Service. It’s your responsibility to keep your phone and access to the app
        secure. We therefore recommend that you do not jailbreak or root your phone, which is the
        process of removing software restrictions and limitations imposed by the official operating
        system of your device. It could make your phone vulnerable to malware/viruses/malicious
        programs, compromise your phone’s security features and it could mean that the Spaceus app
        won’t work properly or at all.</string>
    <string name="termsCond5">
        The app does use third party services that declare their own Terms and Conditions.</string>
    <string name="termsCond6">
        You should be aware that there are certain things that Spaceus will not take responsibility
        for. Certain functions of the app will require the app to have an active internet
        connection. The connection can be WiFi, or provided by your mobile network provider,
        but Spaceus cannot take responsibility for the app not working at full functionality if
        you don’t have access to WiFi, and you don’t have any of your data allowance left.</string>
    <string name="termsCond7">
        If you’re using the app outside of an area with WiFi, you should remember that your terms
        of the agreement with your mobile network provider will still apply. As a result, you may be
        charged by your mobile provider for the cost of data for the duration of the connection
        while accessing the app, or other third party charges. In using the app, you’re accepting
        responsibility for any such charges, including roaming data charges if you use the app
        outside of your home territory (i.e. region or country) without turning off data roaming.
        If you are not the bill payer for the device on which you’re using the app, please be aware
        that we assume that you have received permission from the bill payer for using the app.</string>
    <string name="termsCond8">
        Along the same lines, Spaceus cannot always take responsibility for the way you use the app
        i.e. You need to make sure that your device stays charged; if it runs out of battery and
        you can’t turn it on to avail the Service, Spaceus cannot accept responsibility.</string>
    <string name="termsCond9">
        With respect to Spaceus’s responsibility for your use of the app, when you’re using the app,
        it’s important to bear in mind that although we endeavour to ensure that it is updated and
        correct at all times, we do rely on third parties to provide information to us so that we
        can make it available to you. Spaceus accepts no liability for any loss, direct or indirect,
        you experience as a result of relying wholly on this functionality of the app.</string>
    <string name="termsCond10">
        At some point, we may wish to update the app. The app is currently available on Android –
        the requirements for system(and for any additional systems we decide to extend the
        availability of the app to) may change, and you’ll need to download the updates if you want
        to keep using the app. Spaceus does not promise that it will always update the app so that
        it is relevant to you and/or works with the Android version that you have installed on your
        device. However, you promise to always accept updates to the application when offered to you,
        We may also wish to stop providing the app, and may terminate use of it at any time without
        giving notice of termination to you. Unless we tell you otherwise, upon any termination,
        (a) the rights and licenses granted to you in these terms will end;
        (b) you must stop using the app, and (if needed) delete it from your device.</string>

    <!--changes to terms and condition-->
    <string name="changes2terms">Changes to This Terms and Conditions</string>
    <string name="termsCond11">We may update our Terms and Conditions from time to time.
        Thus, you are advised to review this page periodically for any changes. We will notify you
        of any changes by posting the new Terms and Conditions on this page.</string>
    <string name="termsCond12">These terms and conditions are effective as of 2021/08/05</string>

    <!--contact us section-->
    <string name="contactUs">Contact Us</string>
    <string name="termsCond13">If you have any questions or suggestions about our Terms and
        Conditions, do not hesitate to contact us at xtjlim001@mymail.sim.edu.sg</string>
    <string name="generatedBy">This Terms and Conditions page was generated by App Privacy
        Policy Generator</string>

    <!--PRIVACY POLICY section-->
    <string name="privacyPol1">Spaceus built the Spaceus app as a Free app. This SERVICE is provided
        by Spaceus at no cost and is intended for use as is.</string>
    <string name="privacyPol2">This page is used to inform visitors regarding our policies with the
        collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information if anyone decided to use our Service.
    </string>
    <string name="privacyPol3">If you choose to use our Service, then you agree to the collection and
        use of information in relation to this policy. The Personal Information that we collect is
        used for providing and improving the Service. We will not use or share your information with
        anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.</string>
    <string name="privacyPol4">The terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our
        Terms and Conditions, which is accessible at Spaceus unless otherwise defined in this Privacy
        Policy.</string>

    <!--information collection and use section-->
    <string name="collectionUse">Information Collection and Use</string>
    <string name="privacyPol5">For a better experience, while using our Service, we may require you
        to provide us with certain personally identifiable information, including but not limited to email.
        The information that we request will be retained by us and used as
        described in this privacy policy.</string>
    <string name="privacyPol6">The app does use third party services that may collect information
        used to identify you.</string>

    <!--log data section-->
    <string name="privacyPol7">We want to inform you that whenever you use our Service, in a case of
        an error in the app we collect data and information (through third party products) on your
        phone called Log Data. This Log Data may include information such as your device Internet
        Protocol (“IP”) address, device name, operating system version, the configuration of the app
        when utilizing our Service, the time and date of your use of the Service, and other statistics.
    </string>

    <!--cookies section-->
    <string name="privacyPol8">Cookies are files with a small amount of data that are commonly used as
        anonymous unique identifiers. These are sent to your browser from the websites that you visit and
        are stored on your device\'s internal memory.</string>
    <string name="privacyPol9">This Service does not use these “cookies” explicitly. However, the app
        may use third party code and libraries that use “cookies” to collect information and improve
        their services. You have the option to either accept or refuse these cookies and know when a
        cookie is being sent to your device. If you choose to refuse our cookies, you may not be able
        to use some portions of this Service.</string>

    <!--service providers section-->
    <string name="privacyPol10">We may employ third-party companies and individuals due to the following reasons: </string>
    <string name="privacyPol11">* To facilitate our Service;</string>
    <string name="privacyPol12">* To provide the Service on our behalf;</string>
    <string name="privacyPol13">* To perform Service-related services; or</string>
    <string name="privacyPol14">* To assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.</string>
    <string name="privacyPol15">We want to inform users of this Service that these third parties have
        access to your Personal Information. The reason is to perform the tasks assigned to them on
        our behalf. However, they are obligated not to disclose or use the information for any other
        purpose.</string>

    <!--security section-->
    <string name="privacyPol16">We value your trust in providing us your Personal Information, thus
        we are striving to use commercially acceptable means of protecting it. But remember that no
        method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure and
        reliable, and we cannot guarantee its absolute security.</string>

    <!--links to other sites section-->
    <string name="privacyPol17">We value your trust in providing us your Personal Information, thus
    we are striving to use commercially acceptable means of protecting it. But remember that no
    method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure and
    reliable, and we cannot guarantee its absolute security.</string>

    <!--children's privacy section-->
    <string name="privacyPol18">These Services do not address anyone under the age of 13. We do not
    knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13 years of age.
    In the case we discover that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information,
    we immediately delete this from our servers. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware
    that your child has provided us with personal information, please contact us so that we will be
    able to do necessary actions.</string>

    <!--changes to this privacy policy section-->
    <string name="changes2policy">Changes to This Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="privacyPol19">We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. Thus, you are advised
        to review this page periodically for any changes. We will notify you of any changes by posting
        the new Privacy Policy on this page.
        This policy is effective as of 2021/08/05</string>

    <!--contact us section-->
    <string name="privacyPol20">If you have any questions or suggestions about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate
        to contact us at xtjlim001@mymail.sim.edu.sg</string>
    <string name="generatedBy2">This privacy policy page was created at privacypolicytemplate.net and
    modified/generated by App Privacy Policy Generator</string>
    <string name="err_msg_enter_locName">Please enter shop name.</string>
    <string name="err_msg_enter_locAddress">Please enter shop address.</string>
    <string name="err_msg_enter_hours">Please enter opening hours.</string>
    <string name="err_msg_enter_amenities">Please enter amenities.</string>
    <string name="err_msg_enter_transport">Please enter transport</string>
    <string name="err_msg_enter_desc">Please enter description.</string>
    <string name="add_success">Add location successfully. Our admin will verify the details and upload on home page.</string>

</resources>